Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1921-1979; Accession 19ND-A-410
  - Series XII
    - APHA (general), 1970-72 (Box 394, Folder 68)
    - Arrangements and Policies for Studies in Clinical Setting, 1969-1973 (Box 394, Folder 69)
    - Basic Program - Historical Data, 1969-71 (Box 394, Folder 71)
    - Appointments Committee, 1969-70 (Box 394, Folder 72)
    - Appointments Committee - Dean's Confidential File, 1967-1969 (Box 394, Folder 73)
    - American Nurses Association Convention - Miami Florida (photographs), 1970 May 3-7 (Box 394, Folder 74)
    - Yale School of Nursing General, 1967-73 (Box 394, Folder 75)
    - Yale School of Nursing Alumnae Association (Dean), 1968-71 (Box 395, Folder 76-77)
    - Admissions Committee, 1970-72 (Box 395, Folder 78)
    - Admissions Committee, 1968-70 (Box 395, Folder 79)
    - Admissions Committee, 1967-68 (Box 395, Folder 80)
  - Series XIII
    - Committee on Research Involving Human Subjects, Record of Committee Action, 1971-1972 (Box 396, Folder 1)
    - Community Affairs, 1969-72 (Box 396, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut Health Association -Task Force to Plan and Reorganize Nursing Service and Nursing Education, 1972 (Box 396, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut League for Nursing, 1969-72 (Box 396, Folder 4)
    - Council of Schools of Nursing in Connecticut, 1969-72 (Box 396, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1969-72 (Box 396, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut Nurses Association, 1971-1972 (Box 396, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1969-72 (Box 396, Folder 8)
    - connecticut State Board of Examiners, 1968-72 (Box 396, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut State Department of Mental Health, 1965-72 (Box 396, Folder 10)
    - Curriculum Committee Proposal -Change in Grading System, 1969 (Box 396, Folder 11)
    - Curriculum Committee (Minutes and Courses), 1967-68 (Box 397, Folder 12-13)
    - Curriculum Committee (Minutes), 1971-73. (Box 397, Folder 14)
    - Report on Triple Commitment Evaluation Committee, 1972 (Box 397, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Triple Commitment, 1970-71 (Box 397, Folder 16)
    - Committee on Triple Commitment and Evaluation (Ad hoc), 1970-71 (Box 397, Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee (Minutes), 1971-1972 (Box 397, Folder 18)
    - Experimental Health Services Planning and Delivery Systems, 1971 (Box 397, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Meetings (Minutes), 1971-73 (Box 398, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Publications, 1971-1972 (Box 398, Folder 21)
    - Project HOPE -Miscellaneous, 1968-72 (Box 398, Folder 22)
    - International -Miscellaneous, 1970-72 (Box 398, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Positions -Inquiries, 1972-73 (Box 398, Folder 24)
    - Joint Administrative Committee, 1970-72 (Box 398, Folder 25)
    - Memos -Miscellaneous (within Yale School of Nursing Administration), 1971-1972 (Box 398, Folder 27)
    - National Fund for Graduate Nursing Education, 1968-72 (Box 398, Folder 29)
    - National League for Nursing Baccalaureate and Higher Degrees, 1972 (Box 398, Folder 30)
    - National League for Nursing -Accreditation, 1971-1972 (Box 398, Folder 31)
    - National League for Nursing -Accreditation -Correspondence, 1968-72 (Box 398, Folder 32)
    - New Haven Health Care Incorporated, 1972 (Box 399, Folder 33)
    - New Haven Organizations -Miscellaneous, 1969-72 (Box 399, Folder 34)
    - Orientation Schedule -Yale School of Nursing, 1971-1972 (Box 399, Folder 35)
    - Pediatric Nursing, 1971-1972 (Box 399, Folder 36)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Institute (Apr 16-20), 1971 (Box 399, Folder 37)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Institute, 1972 (Box 399, Folder 38)
    - Psychiatric Nusing Faculty Meetings (minutes), 1971-1972 (Box 399, Folder 39)
    - Public Health Nursing, 1971-1972 (Box 399, Folder 40)
    - Public Health Nursing, 1969-71 (Box 400, Folder 41)
    - Publicity, 1972 (Box 400, Folder 42)
    - Publicity, 1968-71 (Box 400, Folder 43)
    - Questionnaires and Inquiries (to Yale School of Nursing), 1967-72 (Box 400, Folder 44)
    - Quinnipiac College, 1969-72 (Box 400, Folder 45)
    - Recruitment, 1968-72 (Box 400, Folder 46)
    - Research Seminar, 1972 (Box 400, Folder 47)
    - Schedules -Permanent File, 1966-71 (Box 400, Folder 48)
    - Student Affairs -Memos (E.G. Barnett), 1968-71 (Box 400, Folder 49)
    - Student Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 400, Folder 50)
    - United States Public Health Service -Bureau of Health Manpower, 1969-72 (Box 400, Folder 51)
    - United States Public Health Service -National Center for Health Services -Research and Development, 1969-72 (Box 400, Folder 52)
    - Transcript of Weed Presentation (Mar 28), 1973 (Box 400, Folder 53)
    - Yale School of Nursing -Master's Theses -Readers
      Restricted until January 1, 2047
      - 1964-65 (Box 400, Folder 54)
      - 1966 (Box 400, Folder 55)
      - 1967 (Box 400, Folder 56)
      - 1968 (Box 400, Folder 57)
      - 1968-69 (Box 401, Folder 58)
      - 1970-72 (Box 401, Folder 59-61)
    - Visitors to Yale School of Nursing, 1971 (Box 401, Folder 62)
    - Visitors to Yale School of Nursing, 1969-71 (Box 401, Folder 63)
    - YSN -Dean Search Committee, 1972 (Box 401, Folder 64)
    - YSN -New Roles in Ambulatory Services, 1969-72 (Box 401, Folder 65)
    - YSN -Alumnae College, 1972 (Box 401, Folder 66)
    - YSN -Alumnae College, 1970-71 (Box 401, Folder 67)
    - YSN -Annual Report, 1972 (Box 401, Folder 68)
    - YSN -Research Development, 1968-72 (Box 401, Folder 69)
    - Research Development Luncheon Meetings (minutes), 1968-70 (Box 401, Folder 70)
    - Project Staff Meetings (Research Development Project), 1967-68 (Box 402, Folder 71)
    - Activities -Proposals -Action Comments (re: Research Development Project), 1969-71 (Box 402, Folder 72-73)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, 1972 (Box 402, Folder 74)
    - Yale President Kingman Brewster, 1969-71 (Box 402, Folder 75)
    - Yale Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1969-71 (Box 402, Folder 76)
    - Yale-Fanton, Jonathan -Special Assistant to President (Box 402, Folder 77)
    - Yale University Honorary Degree Recipients, 1968-71 (Box 402, Folder 78)
    - Yale Department of University Health -Advisory Committee on Medical Planning, 1968-71 (Box 402, Folder 79)
    - Yale -Personnel Office, 1972-73 (Box 402, Folder 80)
    - Yale -Provost Charles Taylor, 1971-1972 (Box 403, Folder 81)
    - Yale in China, 1969-72 (Box 403, Folder 82)
    - Yale -Department of Psychiatry, 1968-72 (Box 403, Folder 83)
    - Advanced Training in Liaison Psychiatry, MH 10466-08 (Dr. Hoyle Leigh), 1972 (Box 403, Folder 84)
    - Yale Schoool of Medicine -Office of Regional Activities, 1970-71 (Box 403, Folder 85-86)
    - Yale University, Structure, Governance, etc., 1969-72 (Box 403, Folder 87)
    - Yale -Study of Ethical Problems of the Professions -Dr. Solnit et al., 1971 (Box 403, Folder 88)
    - Yale -Treasurer's Office: J.E. Ecklund, 1966-72 (Box 404, Folder 89)
    - University Health Board, 1971-1972 (Box 404, Folder 90)
    - Yale New Haven Medical Center Ambulatory Services, 1969 (Box 404, Folder 91)
    - Yale New Haven Medical Center -Anna Ryle, 1968-72 (Box 404, Folder 92)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital -Trauma Project (Dr. Cole), 1971 (Box 404, Folder 93)
    - Yale School of Nursing -Reference Room.-Files, 1971-1972 (Box 404, Folder 94-95)
    - Maternal -Newborn Nursing Program, 1971-1972 (Box 404, Folder 96)
    - Pediatric Nusing Program, 1971-1972 (Box 404, Folder 97)
    - Psychiatric Nusing Program, 1971-1972 (Box 404, Folder 98)
    - Public Health Nursing Program, 1971-1972 (Box 404, Folder 99)
    - Research Program, 1971-1972 (Box 405, Folder 100)
    - Students, 1971-1972 (Box 405, Folder 101)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program, 1971-1972 (Box 405, Folder 102)
    - Faculty Curriculum Vitae, 1971-1972 (Box 405, Folder 103)
    - Yale School of Nursing Progress Report to President Griswold, 1961 (Box 405, Folder 104)
    - Report to the President: Nursing Education at Yale, 1962 (Box 405, Folder 105)
    - Report to President Griswold: Yale and Nursing Education, 1962 (Box 405, Folder 106)
    - Yale School of Nursing Self-Eva1uation-Report (Feb 1), 1972 (Box 405, Folder 107)
    - YSN Self Evaluation Report (Feb 21) 2 copies, 1964 (Box 405, Folder 108)
    - YSN Alumnae Association (Revised By-laws), 1971-1972 (Box 406, Folder 109)
    - YSN -Annual Report, 1970 (Box 406, Folder 110)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society -Commission on Allied Medical, 1972 (Box 406, Folder 111)
    - Ambulatory Services-Mr. Paris' plan, 1971 (Box 406, Folder 112)
    - American Association of Deans of College and of Nursing, 1971-72 University Schools (Box 406, Folder 113)
    - American Nurses' Association, 1968-72 (Box 406, Folder 114)
    - American Nurses' Association Convention, Apr 30 -May 5, 1972 (Box 406, Folder 115)
    - Appointments Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 406, Folder 116)
    - Appointments Committee, 1970-71 (Box 406, Folder 117)
    - Appointment Committee, 1970 (Box 406, Folder 118)
    - Basic Program -Interim Planning Committee, 1972 (Box 406, Folder 119)
    - Bellas Lecture, 1965-72 (Box 407, Folder 120)
    - Christmas Party Information -Yale School of Nursing, 1964-70 (Box 407, Folder 122)
    - Clinical Facilities-Yale New Haven Hospital, 1968-72 (Box 407, Folder 123)
    - Commencement, 1972 (Box 407, Folder 124)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Behavioral Sciences, 1972 (Box 407, Folder 125)
    - Committee on Community Health Services, 1971-73 (Box 407, Folder 126)
    - Committee on Education of Allied Health Personnel, 1971-1972 (Box 407, Folder 127)
  - Series XIV
    - Abstracts -Address File, Letters and Requests, 1968-72 (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Abstracts of Studies in Nursing -Requests, 1973 (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Accreditation -Midwifery, 1972 (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Evaluation, 1972-73 (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Admissions Committee, 1972 (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Committee on Continuing Education, 1972 (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Alumnae College -Yale School of Nursing, 1973 June (Box 408, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Contributions, 1972-73 (Box 408, Folder 8)
    - Alumnae Council, 1971-73 (Box 408, Folder 9)
    - American Association of Colleges of Nursing, 1973 (Box 408, Folder 10-11)
    - American Nurses' Association, 1973 (Box 408, Folder 12)
    - Annual Report Yale School of Nursing, 1972-73 (Box 409, Folder 13)
    - Annual Report, YSN, 1971 (Box 409, Folder 14)
    - Appointments in Clinical Track -YSN, 1971 (Box 409, Folder 15)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1973 (Box 409, Folder 16)
    - Association of Community Health Service Agencies, 1971-73 (Box 409, Folder 17)
    - Building and Space Information -YSN, 1973 (Box 409, Folder 18)
    - Clinical Arrangements for Master's Studies, 1973 (Box 409, Folder 19)
    - Commencement, 1973 (Box 409, Folder 20)
    - Committee on New Health Professionals, 1973 (Box 409, Folder 21)
    - Community Health Care Center Plan, 1973 (Box 409, Folder 22-24)
    - Community Health Care Center Plan, 1973 (Box 410, Folder 25-26)
    - Community Health Care Center Plan, 1971-1972 (Box 410, Folder 27-28)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1972-73 (Box 410, Folder 29)
    - Connecticut -Miscellaneous, 1971-73 (Box 410, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence -Request for Published Articles, 1973 (Box 410, Folder 31)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1972-73 (Box 410, Folder 32)
    - Curriculum Committee -Final Report -A Survey of present YSN curricular needs, 1973 (Box 410, Folder 33)
    - Dean Diers -Proposal, 1973 (Box 411, Folder 34)
    - Donna Diers, Dean -Personal, 1972-73 (Box 411, Folder 35)
    - D. Diers -Correspondence re Yale Alumni Magazine article, 1972-74 (Box 411, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Doctoral Program, 1971-1972 (Box 411, Folder 37)
    - Doctoral Study -YSN Proposal, 1971 (Box 411, Folder 38)
    - Executive Committee, 1972-73 (Box 411, Folder 39)
    - Film Committee Action, Minutes, Notations, 1963 (Box 411, Folder 40)
    - Health Services and Mental Health Administration, 1971-73 (Box 412, Folder 42)
    - Human Services Coalition to the New Haven Foundation, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 43)
    - International Health, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 44)
    - Inquiries -Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 45)
    - Issues Seminar, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 46)
    - Joint Administrative Seminar, 1972-73 (Box 412, Folder 47)
    - Master's Reports, 1971-73 (Box 412, Folder 48)
    - Maternal and Newborn Health Nursing -Committee Meeting Minutes, 1971-73 (Box 412, Folder 49)
    - Margaret G. Arnstein Memorial Service, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 50)
    - Medical Surgical -Recruitment field, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 51)
    - Midwifery Licensure and Practice, 1968--3 (Box 412, Folder 52)
    - National Fund for Graduate Education, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 53)
    - National Institute of Health: Division of Nursing (Bureau Of Health Resourses Development), 1971-73 (Box 412, Folder 54)
    - Department of Health Education and Welfare and National Institute of Health- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Newsletter, 1973 (Box 412, Folder 55)
    - NLN Baccalaureate and Higher Degree Programs, 1973 (Box 413, Folder 56)
    - National League for Nursing (General), 1973 (Box 413, Folder 57)
    - New England Board of Higher Education - New England Council of Higher Education for Nurses, 1973 (Box 413, Folder 58-59)
    - New England Council of Higher Education for Nurses, 1973 (Box 413, Folder 60-61)
    - New England Council of Higher Education for Nurses, 1973 (Box 414, Folder 62)
    - New Haven Health Care, Incorporated - Household Survey, 1973 (Box 414, Folder 63)
    - New Haven Health Care, Incorporated - R and E Subcommittee, 1973 (Box 414, Folder 64)
    - New Haven Health Care, Incorporated - Executive Board, 1973 (Box 414, Folder 65)
    - New Haven Institute of Allied Health Careers, Incorporated, 1972-73 (Box 414, Folder 66)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association, 1973 (Box 414, Folder 67)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association, 1970-72 (Box 414, Folder 68)
    - Office of Regional Activities Literature Study (National Science Foundation), 1973 (Box 414, Folder 69)
    - 70 Peterson's Guides, 1973 (Box 414, Folder 70)
    - 71 Philosophy of Yale School of Nursing, 1961 (Box 414, Folder 71)
    - 72 Program Chairmen's Meetings, 1972-73 (Box 414, Folder 72)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Program - Child Psychiatry Track, 1972 (Box 414, Folder 72)
    - 73 Psychiatric Nursing, 1966-73 (Box 414, Folder 73)
    - Public Health Nursing, 1972-73 (Box 415, Folder 74)
    - Publicity, 1973 (Box 415, Folder 75)
    - Publishers, 1970-73 (Box 415, Folder 76)
    - Questionnaires- Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 415, Folder 77)
    - Recruitment - General, 1973 (Box 415, Folder 78)
    - Reference Room Ledger -Library Budget, 1969-71 (Box 415, Folder 79)
    - Reference Room Administration, 1973 (Box 415, Folder 80-83)
    - Research and Evaluation Task Force Minutes, 1973 March 5-22 (Box 416, Folder 84)
    - Universities -Correspondence, Miscellaneous A-K, 1971-73 (Box 416, Folder 85)
    - Universities -L-P, 1971-73 (Box 416, Folder 86)
    - Universities Q-Z, 1971-73 (Box 416, Folder 87)
    - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1969-73 (Box 416, Folder 88)
    - World Health Organization, 1973 (Box 416, Folder 89)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital -Medical Center -Miscellaneous, 1971-73 (Box 416, Folder 90)
    - Yale School of Medicine Community Health -Mental Health, Dr. Coleman, 1970-73 (Box 416, Folder 91)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital, 1972-73 (Box 416, Folder 92)
    - Clinical Scholars Program -Yale School of Medicine, 1972 (Box 416, Folder 93)
    - Yale -School of Medicine -Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969-73 (Box 417, Folder 94)
    - Yale School of Medicine Physicians Associate Program, 1973 (Box 417, Folder 95)
    - Yale School of Medicine -Dean Lewis Thomas, 1972-73 (Box 417, Folder 96)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 417, Folder 97)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, 1970-71 (Box 417, Folder 98)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1972-73 (Box 417, Folder 99)
    - Yale President Brewster, 1969-72 (Box 417, Folder 100)
    - Yale Budget Office, 1969-73 (Box 417, Folder 101)
    - Bursar, 1969-73 (Box 417, Folder 102)
    - Yale -Ralph Burr, Director, Financial Aid (Tuition Postponement Plan), 1971Â·...73' (Box 417, Folder 103)
    - Yale College Report on Summer Term, 1973 (Box 417, Folder 104)
    - Yale Comptroller, 1969-73 (Box 417, Folder 105)
    - Yale Computer -Applications for use of, 1968-73 (Box 418, Folder 106)
    - Yale Office of University Development, 1971-73 (Box 418, Folder 107)
    - Yale -Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1972-73 (Box 418, Folder 108)
    - Yale Graduate Professional Student Senate, 1971-73 (Box 418, Folder 109)
    - Yale Grants and Contracts Administration, 1971-73 (Box 418, Folder 110)
    - Yale -Honorary Degrees, 1972-73 (Box 418, Folder 111)
    - Yale -Housing and Parking Communications, 1969-73 (Box 418, Folder 112)
    - Yale Medical Library, 1972-73 (Box 418, Folder 113)
    - Yale Medical School Council, 1973 (Box 418, Folder 114)
    - Yale Miscellaneous, 1972-73 (Box 418, Folder 115)
    - Yale School of Nursing Parking Information, 1971-73 (Box 418, Folder 116)
    - Yale Deputy Provost: George Langdon, 1973 (Box 418, Folder 117)
    - Yale Provost Richard Cooper, 1972-73 (Box 418, Folder 118)
    - Yale Purchasing, 1972-73 (Box 418, Folder 119)
    - Medical Center Committee on Regional Activities, 1969-73 (Box 419, Folder 11)
    - Yale Secretary's Office -Mr. Chauncey, 1969-73 (Box 419, Folder 121)
    - Yale Treasurer's Office, 1972-73 (Box 419, Folder 122)
    - Yale University Health, 1971-73 (Box 419, Folder 123)
    - Yale Health Board, 1972-73 (Box 419, Folder 124)
    - Yale -Women at Yale, 1972-73 (Box 419, Folder 125)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital -Surgical Associates Program, 1970 (Box 419, Folder 126)
    - Combined Basic Graduate Program Files -Proposal and Start of Program
      - Preliminary Work on Basic Education in Nursing at YSN (Dye and Fitz), 1968 (Box 419, Folder 127)
      - Yale School of Nursing Working Notes (Winter-Spring Term), 1969 (Box 419, Folder 128)
      - Philosophy-Combined Basic Graduate Program Past Drafts, 1972-73 (Box 419, Folder 129)
      - Basic Program, Preparation for, 1969-70 (Box 419, Folder 130)
      - Behavioral Objectives for Graduates (R. Wolf, Consultant), 1974 (Box 420, Folder 131)
      - Combined-Basic Advantages, 1969-70 (Box 420, Folder 132)
      - Combined Basic-Graduate Program - Notes and Discussions, 1968'-70 (Box 420, Folder 133)
      - Combined Basic Program Grant Proposal, Work Notes, 1970 July-October (Box 420, Folder 134)
      - Basic Program - Preparation for, 1969-70 (Box 420, Folder 135)
      - American Nursing Association Council of State Boards of Nursing, Test Plan from State Board, Test pool example, 1971 (Box 420, Folder 136)
      - National Joint Practice Commission Membership Listing, 1973 (Box 420, Folder 137)
      - Nursing Education in the Seventies, 1972 (Box 420, Folder 138)
      - National League for Nursing-Correspondence, 1973 (Box 420, Folder 139)
      - Combined Basic Program Committee, second year (Reworking, Phasing Out), 1969-70 (Box 420, Folder 140)
      - Correspondence re- State Boards and Student Status, 1973 (Box 420, Folder 141)
      - YSN Publicity for Combined Basic Graduate Program, 1973-74 (Box 420, Folder 142)
      - YSN Psychiatric Nursing Curriculum, 1972-73 (Box 420, Folder 143)
      - YSN Maternal Newborn Curriculum, 1972-73 (Box 420, Folder 144)
      - YSH Research Curriculum, 1972-73 (Box 420, Folder 145)
      - Initial Proposal, Connecticut Board of Examiners for Nursing (Box 421, Folder 146)
      - Draft State Board Proposal, February 1974 (Box 421, Folder 147)
      - Plan for Establishment of Combined Basic Graduate Program of Nursing Education, YSN, December 1970 (Box 421, Folder 148)
      - Proposal Submitted to the Department of Health, Education, and and Welfare, for Combined Basic Graduate Program -Original Proposal, 1970 October (Box 421, Folder 149)
      - Drafts - Proposal, 1972 October (Box 421, Folder 150)
      - Objectives - Past Drafts - Combined Basic Graduate Program, 1973 (Box 421, Folder 161)
      - Site Visits and Interviews, 1972-73 (Box 421, Folder 151)
      - Board of Examiners for Nursing, State of Connecticut, 1972-73 (Box 421, Folder 152)
      - Initial Proposal to the Connecticut Board of Examiners for Nursing, March 26,1973 (Box 421, Folder 153)
      - Proposal for a Basic Program in Yale School of Nursing, 1969 July (Box 421, Folder 154)
      - Combined Basic Graduate Program Characteristics of Graduates, 1972 (Box 421, Folder 155)
      - Minutes for Combined Basic-Graduate Program, 1972 September- 1973 May (Box 421, Folder 156)
      - Program Assumptions (4/16/73 - 1/20/74), 1973-74 (Box 421, Folder 157)
      - White Paper - Students Combined Basic-Graduate Program, 1973 (Box 421, Folder 158)
      - Behavioral Objectives for Yale School of Nursing Clinical Nurse Practitioners, 1973 (Box 421, Folder 159)
      - Objectives-Present Draft, Combined Basic Graduate Program (Box 421, Folder 160)
      - White Paper-Program Goals, Combined Basic Graduate Program, 1973-1974 (Box 421, Folder 162)
      - Excerpts from Educational Objectives, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 163)
      - Proposed Design of the First Year, MPCG, 1/25/74, II, 1974 (Box 422, Folder 164)
      - Curriculum Past Drafts - Combined Graduate Program, 1973-74 (Box 422, Folder 165)
      - Course Description # 105 - Combined Basic-Graduate Program, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 166)
      - Course Descriptions # 103, 104a, 104b, 105, 106, 205a, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 167)
      - Curriculum Present Draft Combined Basic Graduate Program, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 168)
      - Curriculum Suggestions from the five basic Yale School of Nursing Departments, 1973 October (Box 422, Folder 169)
      - Admissions and Student Affairs Task Force Committe Minutes and Information, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 170)
      - Combined Basic-Graduate Program Minutes, 1972 (Box 422, Folder 171)
      - Combined Basic-Graduate Programs Minutes, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 172)
      - Combined Basic Graduate Program Correspondence, 1970-72 (Box 422, Folder 173)
      - Combined Program, Recruitment File, 1972-73 (Box 422, Folder 174)
      - Combined Basic Specialization Minutes, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 175)
      - Task Force Work Sheet # 3, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 176)
      - Task Force Work Sheet # 2, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 177)
      - Task Force Work Sheet # 1, 1973 (Box 422, Folder 178)
    - Registration Problems, Miscellaneous data re: Problems in Several States, 1923--8 (Box 423, Folder 179)
    - Registration Problems in Other States -Correspondence, 1941-58 (Box 423, Folder 180)
    - Distribution of Employed Graduates, 1926-58 (Box 423, Folder 181)
    - Clinical Data (Classes of '36-' 58), 1936-qa (Box 423, Folder 182)
    - Data on Graduates and their Occupations/Locations, 1953-56 (Box 423, Folder 183)
    - Impressions of Rooming-In, 1950-51 (Box 423, Folder 184-185)
    - Impressions of Rooming in, 1952 (Box 423, Folder 186)
    - Rooming-In, Patients' Impressions, 1951-52 (Box 424, Folder 1a7)
    - Snoke -Proposal for five year study of Nursing Practice in Hospital, 1958 (Box 424, Folder 188)
    - Maternal-Newborn Program (Historical), 1966-68 (Box 424, Folder 189)
    - Nurse-Practitioner Program -Early Drafts, 1969-71 (Box 424, Folder 190)
    - Ad Hoc Committee for Long Range Planning on Advanced Study (Box 424, Folder 195)
    - Ad Hoc Committee for Long Range Planning for Clinical Practice, 1966-1967 (Box 424, Folder 196)
    - Admissions Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 424, Folder 197)